







Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Summary

Jump to Section

I am currently working as Associate Consultant in LTI. I have completed my B.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering. I am looking forward for opportunity in Control-Mand on Dollar Universe.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

Work Experience

L&T Infote ch as Consultant

Nov 2018 to Till Date

- ? Creating and scheduling jobs on the Dollar Universe and Control-Min Distributed environment (Test and production).
- ? Monitor, research, analyze and report problems to programmer or developer
- ? Build and manage job flows, calenders requirement and scheduling criteria.
- ? Provided support for Disaster Recovery Activities.
- ? Microsoft Outlook for various requests and emails.
- ? Resolving the incidents within SLA
- ? Creating and analyzing incidents, creating and tracking problems till the closure as and when required.
- ? Analyze and fix production incidents/requests.
- ? Report root cause of the incidents and present ideas to prevent the incidents from occurring in future.
- ? Maintaining the shift turnover, which includes the current and the pending information from one shift to another.
- WIPRO as Senior Administrator

Aug 2017 to Dec 2018

Responsible for providing the support in L2/L3 level depending on the Priority of the issues (High, Medium and Low) to meet client SLA

Capgemini as Consultant Jun 2016 to Aug 2017

Scheduling production batch jobs, adhoc requests and performing change requests as per the requirement. Performing analysis on scheduling issues and resolving the same within SLA Defining new jobs and scheduling tables using Control-Mdesktop. Preparing daily status report to share with the Leadership team. Attending customer calls & conference calls to ensure smooth functioning of oncall support.

Tata Consultancy Services as System Engineer

Jan 2013 to Jun 2016

Project 1 TTSL DC

Customer Tata Teleservices Limited

Role Control-M Scheduling and Batch Processing

Description The primary role of Control Mteam is to maintain batch jobs/interfaces in Control M Maintaining batch jobs includes both creation /scheduling and modification of Batch .lobs (and Interfaces)

Jose morado sour d'oduoritodiodamig and modificación el salar cose (and interidoce).

Skills BMC CONTROL-M Scheduling and Administration and worked on Control-M migration

Platforms Linux 5.9,6.4 for server, Windows XP for Workstation

Database Oracle9i, Oracle10g

Development Tools Control -M, TOAD, and Putty

Responsibilities Maintaining (Create/Modify) Control Mjobs and interfaces.

Preparing the reports on the status of Jobs

Configuring and monitoring the jobs through Control ?M

Resolving the issues related to Control ?Mdatabases and application (Administrative part). Managing CONTROL-MServers/agents using CONTROL-MEnterprise Manager version 6.4

System Performance monitoring and troubleshooting by checking CPU, Memory and Disk Utilizations

Worked with AMD process, that includes Stream Pulling and processing CDR?s.

Handling Incident and Problem tickets assigned to Control Massignment group.

Log and update the resolution and recovery of assigned Incidents

System Performance monitoring and troubleshooting by checking CPU, Memory and Disk Utilizations

File systems monitoring and Stream pulling

Other accountabilities included creating process documentation and cross training of existing staff to support the environment long term.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from GANDHI INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY, **GUNUPUR** in 2012

PG: B tech (Computer Science) from Biju Patnaik University of Technology (BPUT) in 2012

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: CONTROL M SCHEDULER CONTROL MADMIN

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Linux, Windows Xp		2016	
Oracle9i , Oracle10g		2016	
Control -M, TOAD, and Putty	Version 8	2017	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Oriya	Proficient			✓
Marathi	Proficient			✓

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: Total is energy trading company of Europe. Control-Mtool is used by TOTAL for automation of batch f

Client: TOTAL

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jun 2016 - Aug 2017 Project Location: Navi Mumbai Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Role: Other Team Size: 10

Skill Used: Control-WEM(v8), UNIX, Endur and Windows.

Role Description: I aspire for a career that would provide me challenging opportunities to assist in advancing a business that offers a stable employment opportunity. I am also eager to learn new skills, business and technological

Project Details: Scheduling production batch jobs, adhoc requests and performing change requests as per the requirement.

Performing analysis on scheduling issues and resolving the same within SLA Defining new jobs and scheduling tables using Control-Mdesktop. Preparing daily status report to share with the Leadership team. Attending customer calls & conference calls to ensure smooth functioning of oncall support

Project Title: TTSL DC

Client: Tata Teleservices Limited Nature of Employment: Full Time Project Location: HYDERABAD

Duration: Jan 2013 - Jun 2016 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Skill Used: BMC CONTROL-M Scheduling and Basics Of Administration Role Description: Maintaining (Create/Modify) Control Mjobs and interfaces,

Preparing the reports on the status of Jobs,

Configuring and monitoring the jobs through Control fivi, Resolving the issues related to Control ?M databases and application, Project Details: The primary role of Control Mteam is to maintain batch jobs/interfaces in Control M Maintaining batch jobs includes both creation/scheduling and modification of Batch Jobs (and Interfaces).

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No**

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.